biosagentplus.com 2011-06-28

# BiosAgentPlus.com - Policies

## Privacy Policy & Terms of Use

**Effective Date:** 10/26/2010 ****

eSupport.com, Inc. has been awarded TRUSTe's Privacy Seal signifying that this privacy policy and practices have been reviewed by TRUSTe for compliance with [TRUSTe's program requirements](http://www.truste.com/privacy_seals_and_services/consumer_privacy/privacy-programs-requirements.html) including transparency, accountability and choice regarding the collection and use of your personal information.  TRUSTe's mission, as an independent third party, is to accelerate online trust among consumers and organizations globally through its leading privacy trustmark and innovative trust solutions. If you have questions or complaints regarding our privacy policy or practices, please contact us at .  If you are not satisfied with our response you can contact [TRUSTe here](http://watchdog.truste.com/pvr.php?page=complaint). The TRUSTe program covers only information that is collected through this Web site, and does not cover information that may be collected through software downloaded from the site.

| [  
](http://privacy-policy.truste.com/click-with-confidence/ctv/en/www.biosagentplus.com/seal_m "Validate TRUSTe privacy certification")  
---|---  
  
**What information do we collect?**   
We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order, subscribe to our newsletter, respond to a survey or fill out a form. 

When registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name and e-mail address.

**What do we use your information for?**  
Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: 

  * **To personalize your experience**  
(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)
  * **To improve our website**  
(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)
  * **To improve customer service**  
(your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)
  * **To process transactions**  
Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested. 
  * We may provide your personal information to companies that provide services to help us with our business activities such as shipping your order or offering customer service. These companies are authorized to use your personal information only as necessary to provide these services to us.
  * **To send periodic emails**  
The email address you provide for order processing, will only be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order. If you decide to opt-in to our mailing list, you will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.  
Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

**How do we protect your information?**  
We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or access your personal information. 

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.

Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies **Cookies** A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user's computer for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies on this site. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site. 

We use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. We use session cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our site. A session ID cookie expires when you close your browser. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. You can remove persistent cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser's "help" file. 

We set a persistent cookie to store your passwords, so you don't have to enter it more than once. Persistent cookies also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. 

If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some areas of our site, such as contests or surveys, will be limited. 

**Tracking Technologies &Third Party Cookies**  
The use of cookies by our partners and affiliatesis not covered by our privacy statement. We do not have access or control over these cookies.

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**  
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**Third party links**  
Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

**Customer Testimonials, Comments & Reviews**  
With your consent we may post your testimonial along with your name. If you want your testimonial removed please contact us at http://esupport.com/feedback.php.

**  
California** **Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**  
Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

**  
Online Privacy Policy Only**  
This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

**  
Terms and Conditions**  
Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at [http://www.esupport.com](http://www.esupport.com/)

**  
Your Consent**  
By using our site, you consent to our [websites privacy policy](http://www.freeprivacypolicy.com/).

**  
Changes to our Privacy Policy**  
We may update this privacy statement to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this Site prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.

**  
Contacting Us**  
If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy, or if you would like to correct, update, change, or delete your information you may contact us using the information below: 

120 Water St., North Andover, MA 01845, USA
